A Finding Aid to the James Graham & Sons Gallery Records, 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011, bulk 1950s-1980s, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1947-2004; 1912; Series 2; 8 Linear feet Boxes 16-24
  - Visionary Artists (circa late 1981-1982) [Cancelled Exhibition], 1981-circa 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - "Krazy Kat" (Jan. 16 - Feb. 6, 1982), 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 7-9)
  - "New York Visionaries" (May 18 - June 25, 1982), circa 1982 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "Pertaining to Boston" (Sept. 1 - Oct. 8, 1982) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - "Lucy Mitchell: Collages and Drawings" (Sept. 15 - Oct. 9, 1982), 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "Six Leading Contemporary Scottish Painters" (Dec. 10, 1982 - Jan. 15, 1983), 1976; 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 13-19)
  - "Pogo" by Walt Kelly (1983), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Illustration Exhibition, "March" (Mar. 1983), 1982 (Box 20, Folder 21-22)
  - "Seymour Fogel: Drawings From the Woodland Portfolio, 1971" (Mar. 2 - Apr. 1, 1983), 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - "Lucy Mitchell: Collages and Drawings" (Sept. 27 - Oct. 22, 1983), 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Calfee, William and Patricia Friend, "Recent Paintings" (Dec. 3-30, 1983), 1972-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - De Niro, Robert (Mar. 13 - Apr. 7, 1984) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - "Mark Adams: Watercolors and a Tapestry" (June 13 - July 6, 1984), 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - "Women: A Changing Picture" (June 18 - Aug. 31, 1984) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - "Four Danish Potters" (1986-1987), 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 1930s and 1940s Women Artists [circa 1988] (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Chicago International Antiques Show (1988), 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - [Group Show (Summer 1988)] Installation Shots, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "The Art Show" (1989), 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Chicago International Antiques Show (1989) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "The Art Show" (1990), 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Chicago International Antiques Show (1990), 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - "Landscape on Paper" (Nov. 29 - Dec. 22, 1990; Graham Modern), 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "Selections" Group Show (Jan. 4-30, 1991; Graham Modern), 1987-1991 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - "The Art Show" (1991), 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
  - Art Shows, Brochure for Graham Gallery, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - "Monotypes" (Feb. 2-23, 1991; Graham Modern), 1984-1991 (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
  - Summer Group Show (June 10 - Aug. 2, 1991; Graham Modern) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - "The Art Show" (1992), 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - "American 19th and Early 20th Century Paintings, Watercolors and Sculpture: The Collection of Kathyrn and Robert Steinberg," Info on Paintings Not Related to Show (1993), 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 23-24)
  - "The Art Show" (1993), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "The Art Show" (1994), 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "The Art Show" (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Bronze Show (May 18 - June 30, 1995) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Narrative" (Nov. 9 - Dec. 23, 1995), 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - "Anima Mundi" (Jan. 18 - Mar. 2, 1996), 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "The Art Show" (1996), 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "The Art Show" (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
  - "Landscape as Abstractions" (Feb. 27 - Apr. 5, 1997), 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "Drawings" (Jan. 29 - Mar. 7, 1998), 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "The Art Show" (1998), 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "The Art Show" (1999), 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "Pattern" (June 24 - Aug. 27, 1999), 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - "Contemporary British Ceramics" (Jan. 13 - Feb. 19, 2000), 1999-2000; 2003 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "The Art Show" (2000), 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "Fluid Flow" (June 22 - Aug. 25, 2000), 2000-2001; 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17-20)
  - "Cascade of Scales" (Jan. 24 - Feb. 23, 2002), 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Holiday Exhibition (2002), circa 2002 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - "Nature Photography" (2003; JG|Contemporary), 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "Grisaille" (Mar. 28 - Apr. 26, 2003); JG|Contemporary) (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - "Selected British Ceramics" (May 2-31, 2003; JG|Contemporary), 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Uptown|Downtown" (June 5 - July 2, 2003; JG|Contemporary), 2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Contra/post" (Nov. 15 - Dec. 20, 2003; JG|Contemporary) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "Wood Work" (July 16 - Aug. 20, 2004; JG|Contemporary) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Guest Books, 1993-2001; 1959-1961; (12 books) (Box 23, Folder 8-17)
  - Guest Books, 2001-2002; (2 books) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Artists' Files, bulk 1955-1999; circa 1907-2006; Series 3; 39.1 Linear feet Boxes 24-62, 95-96
  Artists' Files documents the relationship or interest the gallery had with individual artists, especially modern American artists. Folders for each artist can contain a variety of materials, such as correspondence with the artist, clients, galleries, and museums regarding consignments, exhibitions, loans, and sales; photographs, slides, and transparencies, primarily of artwork; sales invoices; exhibition catalogs, postcards, and other printed materials; press releases; magazine and newspaper clippings, often compiled in binder sleeves; price lists and related exhibition records; artist binders containing biographical information and photographs; and research materials on artists and artwork. Also found are some scattered subject files, per original arrangement.
  There is extensive material related to artists Carmen Cicero, Susan Crile, Elaine De Kooning's portrait of President John F. Kennedy, Edwin Dickinson, muralist Seymour Fogel, Nancy Fried, Irving Kriesberg, Gari Melchers, Jonathan Santlofer, Reeve Schley, Peter Stevens, Joan Thorne, and Selina Trieff. Researchers are encouraged to also consult Alphabetical Files when researching particular artists or artworks.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by artists' last name or subject.
  - A-C, Miscellaneous, circa 1956-1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Abdell, Douglas, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Abeles, Sigmund, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Abularach, Rodolfo, 1961; 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Ackerman, James, "Abstract Art and the Critics", 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Mark, Sales, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Albert, Calvin, circa 1967 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Alma-Tadema [and Guy Pène Du Bois], 2003; undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - American Abstract Artists, circa 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - American Abstract Artists, Cataloged Drawings, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - American Abstract Artists, General Information, 1979-1989 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - American Abstract Artists/Modernism Spring Show (1987), circa 1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Anderson, Lennart, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Lennart (Box 24)
    - Clippings, 1962-1972 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - [Correspondence], 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - [Inventory and Sales], 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1962-1974 (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
    - Posters and Catalogs, 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 20-21)
  - Anshutz, Thomas, 1962-1967; 1942; circa 1907 (Box 24, Folder 22-23)
  - Anshutz, Thomas (Box 24)
    - Catalog, circa 1963 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence with Edward Anshutz, 1959-1963 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Anshutz, Thomas (Box 25)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1963-1978; 1917 (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
    - Publicity, 1963; 1942 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
    - Sold, undated; 1987; 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Anuszkiewicz, Richard, 1979-1993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Anuszkiewicz, Richard (Box 25)
    - Catalogs, 1976-1984; 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Clients, 1984-1985; 1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Expenses, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Photographic Materials, 1970s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 11-12)
    - Press Binder, circa 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - "Print" Catalog With Notations, 1980s (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Traveling, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Archipenko, Alexander, 1954-1956 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Arp, Jean, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Ase, Arne, 1985-1986; 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Ashlock, Rex, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Ault, George, 1964-1973 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Autorino, Lucia (Salamme), 1956 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Avery, Milton, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Ayrton, Michael, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Balart, Waldo, undated; 1967-1972 (Box 25, Folder 24-26)
  - Baroque, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Bartlett, Paul Wayland, "Sundance" or "Ghost Dance", circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Bartos, Edna, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Beall, Nina, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Beall, Nina (Box 26)
    - Photographic Materials, 1980s (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Press Binder, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Sales, 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Beauchamp, Robert, 1966-1976 (Box 26, Folder 8-10)
  - Beauchamp, Robert, Sales, 1966-1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Beaux, Cecilia, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Beerman, Miriam, 1968-1979 (Box 26, Folder 13-15)
  - Bellotto, Bernardo, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Benin, circa late 1950s; 1935 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Benjamin, Gershon, 1984-1992 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Bentley, Claude, 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Benton, Thomas Hart, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Ben-Zion, 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Ben-Zion, Portfolios, 1955-1957; 1951 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Berke, Ernest, circa 1981 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    Oversized material housed in Box 96, Folder 1
  - Berman, Sarah, 1959-1961 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Bernstein, Theresa, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Bewly, Murray, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Bianco, Pamela (Box 26)
    - Cats and Reviews, 1922; circa 1915; 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      Contains original artwork
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987; 1995; 1969-1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Lists and Agreemens, 1963-1985 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Bianco, Pamela, "Works in Miniature" (Nov. 30 - Dec. 24, 1976) [Includes Victoria Fairbanks and Anthea Lewis] (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Biddle, George, circa 1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Bingham, Geroge Caleb, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Bisttram, Emil, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Blair, Elizabeth, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Blechman, R.O., 1978-1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Bluemner, Oscar, 1956-1969; 1945 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Bluemner, Oscar, Correspondence with Vera Bluemner Kouba, 1959-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Bluemner, Oscar, Exhibition (Dec. 1-30, 1967), 1916; 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Bourdelle, Pierre, 1978; 1969-1971; 1985-1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Bowden, Harry, circa 1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Bowen, Paul, 1981-1986 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Bowen, Paul (Box 27)
    - [Press Binder], 1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Sales, 1985-1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Sales, Accounts, Etc. (1986), 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Bowen, Ron, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Bradshaw, Dove, 1977-1980 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Bragwyn, Frank, Sir, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Broderick, Patricia, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Brown, Judith (1966-1967), 1969; 1960s (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Buecher and Harpsichords, circa 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Burkhardt, Hans, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Butterworth, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Butterworth, Elizabeth, Consignments and Sales, 1993-1996; 2000 (Box 27, Folder 24-25)
  - Cage, John, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Cahillane, Glenda, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Cahillane, Glenda, Correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Calfee, William, 1957-1962 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Callaway, Loren, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - J. Camp Designs, circa 1990 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Canin, Martin, Exhibition Announcements, 1973-1978 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Canin, Martin, Sales, 1967-1981 (Box 27, Folder 33-34)
  - Carles, Arthur Beecher, [Correspondence], 1958-1972 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Carles, Arthur Beecher (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition (Apr. 14 - May 9, 1959) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1941; 1957-1977 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - Publicity, 1946-1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Carsman, Jon, 1969-1976 (Box 28, Folder 6-9)
  - Carsman, Jon, Installation of Works, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cassatt, Mary, 1957-1962 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Castor, Harold, circa 1973 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Chabor, Moura, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Chen, Chi, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Christie, Arthur N., 1985-1990 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Christy, H.C., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Church, Frederic Edwin, 1969-1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Ciccone, Antonio, 1974-1978 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Cicero, Carmen (Box 28)
    - Artist Accounting and Sales Invoices, 1984-1990 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - [Biographical Information], 1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Catalogs and Postcards, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Clients, circa 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1984-circa 1990 (Box 28, Folder 23-25)
    - [Exhibit With June Kelly Gallery (1988)], 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - [In/Out], circa 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Photographic Materials, circa 1984-1990 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Cicero, Carmen, [Press], 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Cicero, Carmen, Traveling, 1984-1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Clark, James L., "Animal Sculpture" (May 1-21, 1957), 1957-1959 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Clutz, William, 1972; 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Coheleach, Guy, 1971-1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Cole, Thomas, "Diminuative Works, Thomas Cole - Thomas Benton" (Summer 1974) (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Collins, John Ireland, 1969-1973 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Cope, George, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Cornwell, Dean, 1978-1985 (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
  - Craig, Nancy Ellen, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Crile, Susan, 1994-1997; 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 12-16)
  - Crile, Susan (Box 29)
    - (1998), 2004; 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - (2001), 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Biographies and Statements, 1990; 1995 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence Through 1993, 1984-1995 (Box 29, Folder 20-21)
    - "The Fires of War" (June 10 - July 31, 1994; Blaffer Gallery), 1994-1998 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Mailing List, circa 1987 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Press, 1980-1995 (Box 29, Folder 24-26)
    - Prices, circa mid-1980s-early 1990s (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Crile, Susan (Box 30)
    - Sales Invoices, 1984-1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Transparencies, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Traveling, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Crouse, Eanger Irving, 1990s (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Crowl, Robert, 1970-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5-6)
  - Curry, John Steuart, 1969-1975 (Box 30, Folder 7-9)
  - Dabo, Leon, 1938; 1960-1977 (Box 30, Folder 10-12)
  - Dalen, Anton van, 1968-1974 (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
  - [Danish Ceramics], 1985-1989 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Danish Ceramics, Correspondence, 1988-1997 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Dash, Robert, 1967-1975 (Box 30, Folder 17-19)
  - Davies, Arthur B. (To Feb. 1967), 1961-1967 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Davis, Warren, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - De Kooning, Elaine, 1959-1983 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - De Kooning, Elaine (Box 31)
    - Clippings, 1959-1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - President John F. Kennedy, 1962-1964 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - President Kennedy, 1962-1964 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - President Kennedy (con't.), 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 8-9)
    - Sales, 1963-1972 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - De Laittre, Eleanor, 1982-1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - De Niro, Robert, 1976-1984; 1961 (Box 31, Folder 12-16)
  - De Niro, Robert, Exhibition Catalogs, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - De Niro, Robert, Writings, 1976; 1984 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Delauney, Robert, 1959-1961 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Delsener, Roland [Rembrandt Bugatti], 2004 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Deming, Edwin Willard, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Detre, Roland, 1955-1958 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Di Leo, Ricatto, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Dibble, Thomas Reilly, 1955-1960 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Dickinson, Edwin, 1961-1968 (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
  - Dickinson, Edwin (Box 32)
    - [Artists' Binder], circa 1961-1979 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs and Magazines, 1959-1982 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
    - "Edwin Dickinson" by Lloyd Goodrich, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Estate Correspondence, 1961-1986 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
    - Exhibition Correspondence, 1976; 1960-1969 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
    - General Correspondence, 1965-1986 (Box 32, Folder 13-14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958-1974 (Box 32, Folder 15-16)
    - National Academy of Design Exhibition (1982), 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - [Photographs Binder] 1914-1942, circa 1960s (Box 32, Folder 18-19)
  - Dickinson, Edwin (Box 33)
    - [Photographs Binder] 1943-, circa 1960s (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Publicity, 1960s-1982 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - [Sales and Accounts], 1961-1972 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
    - (To Feb. 1967), 1961-1968 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Dine, Jim, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Dodge, William, 1982-1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Dole, William, 1956-1963 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Dove, Arthur, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Downes, Rackstraw, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Drewelowe, Eve, 1987-1989 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Drewes, Werner, 1984-1990 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Drexler, Sherman, 1964-1970 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Du Bois, Guy Pène, 1983; 1969 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Duesberry, Joellyn, 2002-2006 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Duesberry, Joellyn (Box 33)
    - College of the Atlanta Exhibition (Aug. 1996) (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Exhibition With Lizan-Tops (1996) (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Fall Exhibition (1996), 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Dunoyer de Segonzac, André, 1935; 1939; undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Durchanek, Ludvik, 1950; 1957-1973 (Box 33, Folder 20-23)
  - Durchanek, Ludvik, Biographies, circa 1961 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Durchanek, Ludvik, Clippings, 1960-1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Durchanek, Ludvik, Photographs, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 34, Folder 2-3)
  - Dutch Show, undated; 1958 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Dye, Charlie, Limited Edition Book, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Dye, Charlie, Unlimited Edition Book, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Eakins, Thomas, 1947; 1944 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ehrenworth, Andrew, 1996-1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Ehrenworth, Andrew (Box 34)
    - (1999), 1999-2002 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Clementine Gallery, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Press, 1996-1999 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Eilshemius, Louis, 1956-1969 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Elliott, Anne, 1976-1984 (Box 34, Folder 13-14)
  - Elliott, Anne, Catalogs and Publicity, 1978-1984 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Ensor, 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Epstein, Jacob, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Evans, Charlotte Cushman, 1987-1991 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Fairbanks, Victoria, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Feibleman, Dorothy, Correspondence, Sales and Photographs, circa 1980s-1992 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Feibleman, Dorothy, Prices, Inventory and Consignments from D.F., 1985-1992 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Ferguson, Kathleen, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Ferguson, Kathy (Box 34)
    - [Press Binder], 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Sales, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Traveling, circa 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Fernandez, Augustin, 1955-1960 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Ferren, John, circa 1987 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Figurative Artists, 1965-1971 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Fine, Perle, 1960-1972; 1988; 1991 (Box 34, Folder 29-31)
  - Fiori, Joseph, 1975-1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Fisher, Davira, 1953-1957 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Fisher, Everett, 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Flanagan, Terry, circa 1966-1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Flannagan, John, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Fleischmann, Adolf, 1960s (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Fogel, Seymour (Box 35)
    - (1984), 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - (1986-1989), 1984-1989 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Advertising Account, circa 1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - [Biography], circa 1989 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - [Consignments], 1987-1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1950s; 1981-1989; 1971 (Box 35, Folder 12-14)
    - Damaged Abstraction - Yellow and Black, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Ethyl Silicate Petroleum Club Mural [and other murals and artwork], 1950s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - [Exhibition Catalogs], 1981; 1956-1957; 1984 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - [Exhibition Postcards], 1980s (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - [Exhibition Printed Materials], 1950s-1960s (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Fogel Estate, 1981-1991 (Box 35, Folder 20-21)
    - Fogel Estate Contracts and Correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Fogel Estate Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - [In/Out], 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Invoices, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Master Lists, 1984; 1990 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Memorial, 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Fogel, Seymour (Box 36)
    - [Miscellaneous], circa 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - [Miscellaneous Correspondence and Documentation], 1987-1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - [Photographic Materials], circa 1950-1980s (Box 36, Folder 3-11)
    - Press, circa 1967-1989 (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
    - [Press Binder], 1950s-1989 (Box 36, Folder 14-15)
  - Fogel, Seymour (Box 37)
    - [Press] Reviews, 1950s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Restorations, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Foley, Vivienne (1995-1997), 2002 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Foster, Tony, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Foujita, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Fox, Connie, 1960s (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Fransioli, Thomas, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - French, Jared, circa 1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Fried, Nancy (Box 37)
    - Accounting - Sold Invoices, 1987-1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Biographical Information, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Biography [and Essays], circa 1989-1991 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Catalogs, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Consignment In, 1989-1990; 1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Consignment Out, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 37, Folder 15-18)
    - European Galleries, circa late 1980s-early 1990s (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition (Sept. 26 - Nov. 2, 1991), 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 20-21)
    - Inventory, 1989-1991 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Joan Whitney Payson Gallery of Art, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Mailing List, circa 1989-1993 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1993 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - "New Work" (Feb. 18 - Mar. 27, 1993) (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Press, 1986-1994 (Box 37, Folder 27-29)
      Includes 1 sound cassette
  - Fried, Nancy (Box 38)
    - Press, 1988-1993 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Press and Photographs, 1985-1993 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Slides, circa 1985-1992 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
    - Transportation, 1993; 1991 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Works Returned to Artist, 1989-1993 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Frost, A.B., 1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Fruhauf, Aline, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Fuseli (Fussli), circa 1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Fussell, Charles Lewis, 1970s (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - G-I, circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Gallo, Frank, 1964-1973 (Box 38, Folder 12-14)
  - Gallo, Frank (Box 38)
    - Artist's Binder, 1964-circa 1967 (Box 38, Folder 15-17)
    - (Old), 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Publicity, 1963-1973 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Gallo, Frank, Sales, 1965-1969 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Gamble, Edwin, 1967-1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Gammell, R.H. Ives, 1976; 1981 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Garman, Ed, 1968; 1983-1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Garston, Gerald, 1966-1970 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
  - Ghikas, Pano, 1956-1960 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Gladstone, Gerald, 1964; 1968 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
  - Glankoff, Sam, 1980-1984 (Box 39, Folder 10-12)
  - Glarner, Fritz, 1955-1983 (Box 39, Folder 13-16)